
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>JSTV Solutions</title>
  <subtitle>JSTV Solutions news in English.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/" />
  <updated
    >2025-01-28T00:00:00Z</updated
  >
  <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>JSTV Solutions</name>
    <email>webmaster@jstvsolutions.com</email>
  </author>
    <entry>
      <title>We Helped a Small Business Grow</title>
      <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/we-helped-a-small-business-grow/" />
      <updated>2025-01-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/we-helped-a-small-business-grow/</id>
      <content type="html"
        >
&lt;p&gt;
  Everyone has their favorite coffee shop, taco stand, or burger joint, and
  those of us at JSTV Solutions are no exception. One of our co-founders has
  been going to the same coffee shop for over a decade, and has gotten to know
  the staff and owners well.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  One day, one of the coffee shop owners was lamenting how slow and difficult it
  was for his customers to use their website. The website had not been updated
  in a while, and he was receiving notifications about security vulnerabilities
  that he didn&#39;t understand. He had reached out to some website builders who
  were offering really expensive rewrites that involved a bunch of techno mumble
  jumble he also didn&#39;t understand.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  This problem was taking up too much of his time and took him away from running
  his business. We offered to take a look, and came up with a plan to move their
  website over to Squarespace. It was quick and cheap, and now they have a
  website that they can update and easily maintain on their own. While we
  normally work on hard, complex problems, we also really love simple solutions.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <title>We Delivered on a Short Timeline</title>
      <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/we-delivered-on-a-short-timeline/" />
      <updated>2025-01-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/we-delivered-on-a-short-timeline/</id>
      <content type="html"
        >
&lt;p&gt;
  Our client makes advanced digital beamforming telemetry systems for the
  aerospace industry. They were working on numerous projects in parallel, each
  with an aggressive deadline. They needed someone who could come up to speed
  quickly, be responsible for some key components, and deliver on time and on
  budget with minimal supervision.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  They tapped JSTV Solutions because of the work that one of our co-founders had
  already done in this area. We designed and implemented a client/server
  protocol, and built a sophisticated, native desktop app in Qt which our client
  used to test and control their telemetry systems. It was a challenge, but we
  met every milestone much to the delight of their customers.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <title>Go Above the Clouds With JSTV Solutions</title>
      <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/go-above-the-clouds-with-jstv-solutions/" />
      <updated>2024-04-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/go-above-the-clouds-with-jstv-solutions/</id>
      <content type="html"
        >
&lt;p&gt;
  Our client uses Amazon Web Services (AWS), including OpenSearch, to provide
  their end users with insights into their IT infrastructure, such as known
  security vulnerabilities and detection of active attacks. As usage of their
  SaaS product increased, our client&#39;s AWS bill grew and their end users
  suffered extreme latencies.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  JSTV Solutions reviewed their architecture and provided them with a summary of
  improvements to make, which included how they ingested and indexed their data,
  as well as the queries they used to search across their large data sets. As a
  result, end user latency averages decreased from 27 seconds to 0.5 seconds,
  and search queries were 94% faster.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <title>Legacy Problems Require JSTV Solutions</title>
      <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/legacy-problems-require-jstv-solutions/" />
      <updated>2024-04-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/legacy-problems-require-jstv-solutions/</id>
      <content type="html"
        >
&lt;p&gt;
  Our client is a family-run retail business and auction house that specializes
  in one-of-a-kind artwork and unique memorabilia. As they have grown over the
  years, they have accumulated disparate software and business processes that
  needlessly wastes time and is error prone. Performing essential business tasks
  such as inventory management, order tracking, and client relationship
  management, became a huge burden for their small team.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  JSTV Solutions built a new, modern e-commerce website that runs directly off
  of their legacy FileMaker database, with the flexibility to further expand
  into customer relationship management and eventually into auction
  functionality. In addition to a reduced workload, the solution provides our
  client with real time inventory management, and access to metrics that will
  give them the insight they need to grow their business without overworking
  their team.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <title>Sumario is Open Source</title>
      <link href="https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/sumario-is-open-source/" />
      <updated>2023-09-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://jstvsolutions.com/en/news/sumario-is-open-source/</id>
      <content type="html"
        >
&lt;p&gt;
  JSTV Solutions is pleased to announce that Sumario, the best way to handle
  forms on any website, is now freely available under the GNU Affero General
  Public License. Its source code, and everything needed to deploy Sumario on
  Fly.io is available on GitLab.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  Tom and Jeff met while in the MBA program at Loyola Marymount University where
  their ambitions to help businesses streamline their operations with simple and
  secure software services collided. First Tom and Jeff developed Ledgery, a
  payroll and tax preparation service for new, small businesses. They
  followed-up with Sumario shortly afterwards. We believe Sumario was the first
  of its kind, and we were pleased to see our idea validated by other, similar
  solutions that came later. However, we never did see the adoption we had hoped
  for and felt Sumario deserved. Sadly, we eventually shelved Sumario in 2017.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  While Tom and Jeff were recently reflecting on the success JSTV Solutions has
  had and discussing our next steps, the idea of reviving Sumario came up. We
  think we&#39;ve learned a lot since we first launched Sumario and have a much
  better chance at making Sumario a commercial success, but at the same time we
  have other responsibilities now that won&#39;t allow us to spend the time on
  Sumario we think that requires. With this in mind we decided to open source
  Sumario.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  Like our passion for remote work, our passion for open source software
  predates its popularity. Tom had already made contributions to Linux, Perl,
  and the Apache web server before the term open source had been invented. We
  knew that Sumario wouldn&#39;t help anyone in its current, archived state. This
  release of Sumario as open source is its most natural evolution to us.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt-8&quot;&gt;
  The only updates we&#39;ve made have been to update Sumario&#39;s dependencies, and
  run it on Fly.io instead of AWS. We believe this really lowers the barrier to
  others to deploy Sumario on their own, but still provides a simple and
  performant service. We&#39;ve created a handful of tickets with some changes we
  think need to be made in the short-term, but we&#39;ve held off on making
  long-term plans. We&#39;re excited to see a community grow around Sumario, and
  look forward to see the direction it wants Sumario to take. We hope you&#39;ll
  join us on this adventure on GitLab. For those who prefer to let someone else
  deploy Sumario for them, we are happy to once again offer Sumario as an
  affordable, paid service at
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://sumar.io&quot; target=&quot;_sumario&quot;&gt;https://sumar.io&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content
      >
    </entry>
</feed>
